# **DUONG THỊ ANH KHOA**

MEDICAL REPRESENTATIVE

# **Objective**

Take advantages of sale/marketing skills, medical information and understanding oftender to become a professional MR (Medical Representative) then a MAS (Market AccessSpecialist) and bring more value to customers. From that, I will contribute to development of thecompany.



# **Education**

## **VO TRUONG TOAN UNIVERSITY**

2011 - 2016

Faculty of Pharmacy

GPA: 3.1/4 (Good)



# **Work Experience**

# **DHA CORPORATION (MEDIC)**

**JULY 2017 - PRESENT** 

MAY 2017 - JULY 2017

Market Access Executive

- Event management the coordination and implementation of internal, external events)
- Handle all stage of market access campaign

#### MERCK EXPORTGMBH

Market Access and Pricing (MAP) Assistant (LEAVE DUE TO PARENTS'SICK)

- Event management the coordination and implementation of internal, external events)
- Supports the PM Marketing Team, MAP -Manager in the execution of the ROPUOperational Plan and in the administrative tasks of the department.

#### **ZUELLIG PHARMA**

SEPTEMBER 2016 - MAY 2017

Hospital Sales Consultant

Handle all the stages of the tender processes, contract (tender, direct purchase, priceapplication). Good relationship with Pharmacy Department of Hospitals and staffs:Pediatric Hospital 2, Binh Tan Hospital, City Hospital, Trieu An Hospital... and someother private hospitals as well as clinics

- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries directly or via phoneand email.
- Help supply goods in time through supporting paperworks, placing andmonitoring orders, solving problems.
- Collect market information, customers' feedback, tender...

# **Certifications**

-TOEIC Certificate with score 800/990

2016



- Ms. Nguyen Thi Bich Thanh (Field Force Manager- Zuellig Pharma): 0918329773
- Mr. Huynh Minh Nghia (Business Manager DHA Corp): 0908007115



- (mag) 27th November, 1992
- 🔼 Female
- **C** 0933 967 902
- 🔳 khoa2711@gmail.com
- PHCMC, Vietnam

# **INTERESTS**

- Learn new things
- Music and travel

### SKILLS

Co-operation

Communication and negotiation

**English Speaking** 

Work under high-pressure

Fast learn